Who am I?
What is my name?
That's right, my name is... I can't not read that as Yulith!
They shouldn't have written it with that font!
Fatal... no, Fetal Fury and Jello.
We're gonna be jello-ing things up in greed.
With Yulith, the second... second of his name.
Oh, we're fat!
We a fat boy!
Oh shit!
Okay, so I see.
It's coming out of the belly button.
That's disgusting.
Oh wait, I also shoot.
Oh!
Oh, that's weird.
I guess I have pretty good range then.
Range is good.
Let's see what we got in here.
A glass eye.
How's that even gonna affect me?
Oh!
Oh, that's nice.
Okay, let me have a look in here.
Discounted Soul Heart.
I don't have any keys, unfortunately.
That's fine.
I'm gonna press the button.
We're gonna see how to... Oh, also two black hearts.
Oh my god, this thing kind of does a lot of damage.
It's not bad.
Oh god, I got hit.
A little confusing.
Kill that guy.
Okay.
Dude, this thing kind of slaps.
Why would I ever shoot when I can do this?
I think it hits them on the way back.
No wait, it's the... Ah, okay, okay.
So we want to do that and then tier follow-up.
That's the way to do that.
Oh my god.
Come here.
Nice.
Oh god.
The sound it makes.
Did we do it?
All right.
Not bad.
I like this character so far.
Seems strong.
Latch key is a Soul Heart and two keys.
Oh, that's actually pretty good for me.
Getting extra keys in green mode is pretty huge.
Don't think we need that one.
I'm gonna buy this, man.
Get a Soul Heart as well.
Thank you.
I could also buy this one.
You know what, I'm buying that and then I'm gonna go inside the... It's a curse room.
I could also open that, but nah.
Two bombs?
Hey, okay.
It's not too bad.
Tropicamide.
More range and increased tier size.
I assume that's gonna increase the range of my... Uh, fetus.
I guess.
Well, get in here.
A jalapeno.
A chance to fire a spectral flame projectile in place of a tier.
Wait, how does that work for me?
Flame projectiles deal heavy damage?
I guess we'll find out.
Wait, what?
That flame came out of my stomach.
Wait, it's only when I... Oh.
It's like guaranteed, I guess, almost.
Wait, I'm gonna... Oh, no, no, nevermind.
It is shooting, okay.
Weird.
Fine.
Let's try it.
Where are you?
Oh, shit.
Oh my god, it does so much damage.
Okay, no problem.
Oh.
Get away from me.
Okay, not bad, not bad.
Good stuff.
Dude, this character seems really strong.
Ten coins.
But wait, we're not done collecting coins, right?
Oh, Jesus.
Oh my god, you're fast.
I cannot run him.
Oh god, it's not going well.
I'm throwing.
Got a mummy here.
Dude, I am slow AF.
I need to find speed.
There's a good amount of knockback on it.
Okay, we're definitely not doing demons.
We're doing angels.
I have started to see the angel side of things.
Demons are bad.
Ah, if I get in there, I can't even open the chest.
I'm not gonna do it.
I do have two bombs.
I could look for a secret, maybe.
Or I could blow that up and actually... Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, I'm gonna move on, I guess.
Oh, definitely destroying that.
Pills, I love it.
Okay, nice.
Wait, how does that work to them?
Makes my little guy shoot faster, I guess.
All right.
Okay, seems solid.
Not too shabby.
Wait, flooded caves down here.
That's cool.
We got one key and we can also enter here, of course.
Nice, more health is good.
Ooh, it's time to pill it up.
Paralysis, great.
May as well use it.
That's very unlucky, man.
It instant destroys poops as well when you fling out the fetus.
Love fetus flinging.
I wonder if this flame can destroy other things.
Sprangler is horrible.
Meat is actually good because it gives me damage as well.
What is it with these paralysis pills?
Stop with the paralysis.
Oh, wait a minute, it's spectral.
Wait, is everything... Hold on a minute.
Okay, no, it's only... Okay, that's kind of cool.
Very nice.
I'm not sure what I want to do.
Just start, I guess.
I'm not overly excited by the items in the shop.
Yeah.
Wait, am I tears?
Wait, am I tears homing?
It kind of feels like they're not shooting straight.
Okay, okay.
Dude, this is so good.
Fletus slinging is great.
Oh, shit, didn't see you there.
Oh, I walked on the goop.
Mistakes were made.
We got a pill.
Shit.
Of course, it's got to be a bad pill.
Terrible pill so far.
This active has done only bad things for me.
Oh, don't even start.
Just get punched.
Punching people with my fetus.
28 coins, solid.
I want this, I guess.
More HP.
Synth oil is also decent.
I wonder if this damage increase also increases the damage of my sort of punching maneuver.
Let's keep fighting.
Whoa!
I'm just keep shooting.
Yeah, look how it's sort of... it's definitely homing.
Look at that!
It's not very good at homing, though.
It's like poor man's homing.
Get away from me.
Not bad.
I think I may... I may actually take this.
Damage in range.
I mean, I have pretty good range already, but we are going to play Space Invaders later, right?
Hopefully.
I could also re-roll, actually.
You know what?
Let's re-roll.
Little baggy.
Two pills at once.
So I can have two shitty pills instead of one.
I don't think so.
A little more re-rolling.
Just one more.
Jesus juice.
Fine.
I'll take it.
Another bad pill.
No, wait.
Do I only get bad pills when I play frickin' Ulyss II?
That's horrible.
So far, it's been only bad pills.
Dude, what do I do against enemies that are fast?
Angel!
I get to choose.
The Halo.
Hold on.
Speed, tears, damage, and range.
That's really good.
Plus one health as well.
I don't care about that guy.
Sacred Heart.
Less tears.
A lot of damage.
Less shot speed.
And another health.
Homing tears!
But I already have homing tears, kinda.
2.3x damage multiplier.
Dude, this is a lot of damage.
If that works with my punch, it's gonna go crazy.
Let me go into here.
I'm gonna waste my one... Oh, okay.
Let me check that out.
Oh, shit!
Hey, it's gonna re-roll for me!
Sick!
Uh, let me see here.
50% chance to heal.
Half a Red Heart.
Ooh!
Placenta!
That could actually be kinda dope.
I'm taking it.
It's discounted, right?
I also have a bomb and a key, but I'm gonna save that for the next floor.
Honestly, the bombs?
I'm not sure what to do.
I mean, I can use the bombs for re-rolling.
Yeah, but I don't have any money right now, so... Oh, shit.
Oh, they're so homing right now.
It's like, next level homing.
All pills are bad!
Maybe I'm just super unlucky?
Or there's actually something to it.
I swear to God, all pills are bad.
This character has all pills bad.
Safety pin.
More range, shot speed, black... yeah, okay.
Bob's rotten head.
That's Isaac throw up a point.
I mean, okay, you know what?
It's better than what I have right now.
Fucking pill sock ass.
Why not?
We can use this to open secrets, right?
Ooh!
Also, I don't get to see my HP right now, so, you know... If I can do this right, I'm gonna hit this and maybe blow a hole here if there's a secret.
Watch, watch, watch, watch.
Okay, okay.
Well, we're gonna get more energy.
Black candle, wire coat hanger, paper clip.
Oh, I can destroy this.
Neat.
I can get in there later.
I don't have any black hearts right now, so I could potentially go in here.
Also, I'm wondering...
If this damage increase I have right now is only on the tears, maybe it's better to just shoot like this.
We'll see.
Get punched, nope.
Let me see.
I mean, okay.
Wait, even my flames are aiming.
Yo, that's crazy.
Not bad.
I think it's affecting both the punch and the tears, honestly.
The damage that is.
It's like a double whammy.
This character is insane.
It's so good.
Oh, shit.
Dude, it's so good at AOE clearing.
The punch.
Nice.
Give me the coins.
We're gonna blow some more shit up now.
Let's try the... Oh, we're gonna blow up here because then we're also gonna get in there.
It's beautiful.
Didn't blow up the rocks.
Huh?
How did that not blow up the rocks?
That's weird.
Immunity to floor curses.
Immunity to negative effects from certain items and... I mean, I like this one, actually.
That means my curse is gone now.
Nice.
Beautiful.
Oh, it's not the good axe, it's the shitty axe.
Okay, whatever.
We also don't have a trinket yet.
I think I may actually go in here.
Dark prince's crown.
While at one red heart, the crown activates and gifts, but I'm not gonna get there.
Whatever.
Loss is power.
Alright, fine.
Kill these guys.
Yeah, nice.
Oh, the punch is still so superior.
I mean, they're both pretty good.
Boom!
Maybe that was a waste.
I should have saved that.
But I'm gonna get more, right?
Okay, no problem.
You're dead, son.
Okay, 13 coins.
Not too shabby.
More tears could be nice as well, but...
Not really.
We didn't get more bombs, unfortunately.
I thought we would get another charge there.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Dude, look at the... I can pretty much just aim from anywhere and this will hit enemies.
Dude, this is kind of sick.
I don't have to think.
I can just focus on dodging.
Ah, we got demons.
But maybe that's good.
Maybe we want demons.
With the black crown or whatever, right?
We take away health.
Two fire rate is kind of a lot, you know?
Actually not a bad idea, but then again, we are on an angel streak right now.
So if I go in there, I'm gonna throw that away, right?
Fuck it, I'm gonna bomb here.
No, wait, no, I'm not.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna bomb on the right side.
I don't think this thing actually... No, no, no, no.
We're gonna get in the chest.
We're probably gonna find a bomb in the chest.
Watch.
Shit.
Well, we have 15 coins now.
Could get more tears.
That's almost like half of the effect of my crown.
Just like that.
It's not a bad idea.
I'm taking it.
Being able to shoot even faster is gonna be good.
I think I'm done here.
Yeah, go.
Here we go.
Okay.
Let's go down here.
Oh, we have no keys anymore.
Ah, more health?
I don't know, man.
Maybe we get an option to re-roll this or something.
What if we find a d6, you know?
Maybe I shouldn't take this yet.
I kind of want to get down to one red heart to make use of my crown.
What's that?
Maggie's faith.
Grants an eternal heart at the start of each new floor.
Whoa.
Okay.
But the problem with this is...
Also, why is it only five?
Probably a trinket.
The problem with this is, if you get it at the start of each new floor, chances are you're gonna lose it, right?
Crackjacks is pretty good.
We get a random trinket from that.
Red candle launches directional flame.
I wonder if there's like a hidden thing where if I get the red candle, it's gonna somehow do something because I also have the black candle.
Maybe they combine and become, I don't know, a crazy candle.
You know what I mean?
Okay, let's just start.
Oh, was there a key in here?
There is a key.
Okay, we can get a key.
Okay, I should just shoot actually.
I can stay at a safe distance and just go crazy.
Dude, this is so strong.
Oh god.
Wow.
Insanity.
Okay.
I love this sound effect.
Oh yeah, look at me.
I'm just gonna sit at a range here and just shoot them.
They all died.
Oh crap.
No problem.
Let's go check for secrets.
I'm gonna frickin...
Damn!
Get me this one.
And you know what?
I'm gonna take this item because fuck it.
Chances are we're not gonna be able to change that.
Dead tooth!
Firing creates an aura around Isaac that poisons enemies.
So I wonder, is that gonna be around me or my little guy?
Ah, too bad.
If it was near my guy, I could just sort of move him into position, you know?
Shit.
That's sad.
Um, crack jacks is more HP.
I guess HP is good.
Oh, we can also do this.
Oh crap.
Oh, I don't even aim in the right direction and the things are still hitting.
Okay, I guess I'll use my last heart here.
Man, what is this shit room?
Boo.
Damn, he died fast.
We got some deeps.
So I tried the right side, we're gonna try left side now.
God damn it, man.
I'm gonna re-roll.
Dealing damage to enemies, recharges.
Active items no longer gain.
Oh, no, no, no, I don't like that actually.
What is that one?
Familiar that fires tears with many random... No.
I don't like any of these, dude.
This is like boring.
Boo.
I think I'll take a cheap key though.
Maybe two, since it's so cheap.
Maybe three.
Okay, we got three keys now, good.
Stay at range, play safe.
Oh God.
Shoot the boss.
Okay, nice.
Damn, no angel again?
I guess we got hit, right?
Damn.
That's fine, it is what it is.
I'm gonna wait.
We're gonna get an angel next time.
We can also donate some HP there.
And then buy hearts, but that's probably not worth it.
I think we move on.
Sad.
If only there was only one charge on my active, you know?
So I could bomb things more often.
Okay.
She very old.
Screw is tears and shot?
I mean, sure.
It's not super exciting, but I take it.
Also, am I actually...
I don't think I've gained any range on my punch, unfortunately.
Mom's pad inflicts fear in all enemies.
No, I'll keep my current.
But I actually pick it up just for the effects.
So we have two out of three on Mom, right?
Okay.
What do we got?
Ball of bandages.
Whoa, that's a new one.
We also need to start saving money at some point here.
Maybe even on this floor.
But I'm really curious about... It's gonna be a familiar for sure, though.
Let me try it.
Oh, it's little Chubby!
Why is that not recognized?
What?
I've seen that already.
That's bullshit.
Ah, damn it!
Ah, okay.
Calm yourself.
Did we just lose all angel chance because of that?
I'm confused.
Oh!
Crap!
Dude, what the fuck?
Pudge him!
What the hell?
I didn't even see that guy.
Oh yeah, I heal because of placenta.
Dude, that actually means we can always get inside a curse room if I'm patient enough.
What if I spam it faster?
Okay, I can actually do quite a bit of high attack rate there with that.
Um...
Yeah, we're just gonna wait until we heal up.
I'm gonna go in the curse room.
Okay.
Bombs are nice, though.
You know, since we're in here...
Damn!
I think I'm about to start saving my HP.
I mean, money.
Oh, shit!
Let me out of there!
Fuck, I was caught in the corner.
That was very scary.
I can't believe it.
We're almost dead.
We're gonna die.
I'm gonna charge across the screen now.
Yeah,
okay.
Whoo!
Scary.
Placenta, do your thing.
Man!
Seriously?
I'm gonna buy some HP here.
I need to play this save.
Honestly, at this point, yes, the idea is to donate money, but I also kinda just wanna...
get wind, you know?
No, I don't want that.
Honestly, though, it could come in handy against the last boss.
Think about it.
When he spawns all those bastards, I do this...
and everyone is feared and I can go crazy, you know?
Actually, kind of a sick strategy.
Oh, now we gain angel chance!
Weird how that works.
Oh, god!
Whoo!
Angels, yes!
Let's see what we get.
More damage or...
Golden aura that deals damage to enemies within it, enemies that take more damage from the aura the closer they are to its center.
I'm gonna take this because I wanna see if it works with my...
Nah, it's still just around my character.
You gotta try it, right?
Hahaha, just punching the angel.
You're dead, son.
Thank you.
I wonder what that can do with these key pieces here.
Finally!
We got a buffer.
Let me see...
Two bombs left.
I could blow this up and...
Yeah, actually do it.
BFF.
That was the damage of familiars.
I wonder if that works with mine.
That sounds crazy if that actually works.
We almost have to try that.
Oh!
Fuck.
I should have taken the spider mod.
I didn't see... I was too fast on the trigger, man.
I think I just wanna leave.
Just go.
It's fine.
The shop.
Show me the money.
I mean the items.
But also, show me the money.
Ooh, nice.
Hahaha!
The fact that I can do that is crazy.
Wow.
Hivemind.
Blue flies and spiders do double damage.
This guy doesn't qualify as a... fly or spider, I guess.
Okay, you know what?
I don't like any of those.
Oh, wait, there's no...
I'm gonna go in here.
Haggle us!
Maybe okay?
I don't know.
We're gonna try it against the last boss.
See if it does something.
Also, we need to save money now.
Oh, my goodness.
Wait, what?
Steamsail.
A bit too late for that, though.
Oh, crap.
Ooh, I don't know what's happening.
Things are just happening.
Whoa!
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I'm doing so much damage.
This is really good.
I am owning it right now.
Okay, we're saving money now.
No more buying.
Um, I will... Oh, you know what I could do?
I could use Haggle us to destroy...
Uh, wait, can I actually use that to destroy secret room walls?
I don't know, actually.
Also, everything is on sale now.
It may be worth it to buy a couple of blue hearts, man.
I... I did say I was gonna save.
But, dude, just a couple.
Three.
We gotta do it.
Oh, my God, he dies fast.
Shit!
What the hell is happening here?
Dude, this boss is nuts.
Jesus.
Okay.
Let me try my little bomb here.
I should have tried that before.
God damn it.
I'm starting to think this bomb doesn't actually work on destroying, um...
secret walls, you know?
Where is he?
Oh, oh my God.
That's a lot.
Jesus Christ.
Angels, baby.
What's that?
Immaculate heart.
Heels all red hearts, chance to fire additional spectral tears that orbit around Isaac.
Fuck yeah, dude.
And a lot of extra damage, I'll take that.
We also get this.
We're gonna blow this guy up as well.
Get punched, nerd.
Dude, my tears are kinda...
Dude, he died fast.
Wow.
Get wrecked, son.
I still don't understand the 11 out of 10 thing on the left.
I have no idea what that means.
Yeah.
Okay, I think we're done here.
I could...
Oh, you know what?
I could blow up the thing over there.
Oh, shit.
They were enemies.
Fanny pack.
No.
Box.
Actually...
Okay, last item I buy.
The very last.
No more after...
See, all pills are bad.
All pills are bad.
It's confirmed.
Golden...
I'm gonna write it down.
Let's see here.
Observations.
Utilith.
The second.
All pills bad.
It's just a native effect.
Of her.
Perth row.
Whoa!
Okay, wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on, hold on.
Maybe this is not the last one that we buy.
Golden horseshoe.
Chance for the...
Ah, that's too late for that.
But we don't have any other trinkets or whatever.
Odd mushroom.
Less damage.
But more tears.
Oh, this could actually be super worth.
This is gonna amplify the damage like crazy.
But we gotta start saving money, man.
This one is...
No, we don't need that.
Yeah, I'm just gonna move.
Wait, turns into a full health pill?
Okay, you know what?
New plan.
Harkalas!
I'm gonna take a...
Wait, where'd the pill go?
Oh, there it is.
I'm gonna take this.
And if I reach one health...
Oh, baby.
We're gonna heal all the way up.
Actually insane strategy.
I'm excited.
Here we go.
Ultra greed.
Wake up.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, wait, I have stuff orbiting myself now.
I don't know what's happening here, man.
Wish me luck.
Heal damage.
Oh, crap.
Oh, the shots are gonna prioritize the little thingies, I guess.
Oh, we're chilling.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
Oh, shit, here we go.
Oh, my God, it's so good at punching them away.
Yoohoo!
Oh, we got him.
We got...
Oh, we got to pick up the money.
No, he's taking it.
He's taking the coins.
Gimme.
Focus, focus.
Look for the monies.
Okay, we're taking some damage here.
There's money everywhere.
You know I'm taking that.
Wait, he's stealing money from me?
How do I have less than 30 suddenly?
No, I don't like that.
Kill them all.
Yeah, you ate nothing.
Easy.
Okay, we don't have a lot of money, unfortunately, but, you know, it's okay.
Didn't unlock anything from that.
That's crazy.
Nice.
Solid.
Ace of clubs has appeared.
All right, guys.
Windstreak of three.
We're actually doing it.
Okay.
I think it's time we start unlocking more new characters.
Let me see here.
Although I also want to play...
Let me see.
We can do Cain.
We're icing.
Dude, we almost have none of these marks on Isaac.
Look at that.
Isaac is naked.
He has nothing.
He has a heart.
Normal mode.
Let's do it.
Okay, let's see here.
The D6 is crazy.
This time I'm really gonna use it.
I always end up not using it because I somehow find items that are so good that I don't want to reroll them.
Okay, go up here.
Oh, I gotta get used to playing with a normal character now again.
We can blow that up.
Nice.
Honestly, I think the plan is to pick that heart up at the end of the first floor.
Just so you don't waste it.
It's a buffer, right?
Shit!
Yeah, that's actually a pretty good strategy.
The key...
More bombs though, please.
Don't take my... don't take my freaking energy!
Scary.
I'm actually gonna go to the boss because I want to use my D6 in there, I guess.
But wait a minute.
I feel like boss items are kind of worse than treasure room items.
Yeah, I'm gonna save it for a treasure room.
Or at least see what's in the treasure room.
Because if it's a shitty item, I want to reroll that, right?
Oh, God.
Weird room.
Oh, nice.
Thanks.
He is so annoying.
Okay.
This is the epileptica.
Lost contact.
Here's collide with and destroy enemy shots.
Mmm, it's pretty good.
But I think I want to reroll it.
Virgo, chance of taking damage to activate a shield, increase the blood.
Oh!
Pills!
Oh, definitely worth.
We're eating pills, baby.
I've had it with these stupid ass shitty pills.
This pill's gonna be good now.
Oh, don't destroy it.
Look at that nice little bow I have on my head.
It's so cute.
There we go.
Thank you.
Nice!
I'm not gonna blow that up for a card.
Cards kind of suck.
Definitely want to buy that pill now.
I'll be back.
If I get more money.
I don't think I can get a full charge for the boss, unfortunately, on my D6.
Unless we find batteries.
Let's just hope for a good item, then.
Why am I yellow?
Look for tinted rocks.
Don't see any.
Oh!
Hey!
Nice!
Not too bad, actually.
Another key.
Well, we're not gonna be wanting for keys.
That's something.
See, I could go in there and lose my buffer or not.
I think I may as well just do the boss first.
It doesn't really matter, I guess.
Yeah, do the boss first.
This guy is the modified version of the Duke.
Oh, there goes the buffer.
Damn it.
Oh my god, this guy is kind of tough.
We need higher DPS.
Oh my goodness.
Get that DPS in there.
Get away from me.
Almost.
There we go.
Hey, we got a little buffer there.
Ah!
I should have taken that!
I hate myself.
I shouldn't have taken that buffer yet.
We're going in with no buffer.
I wanna do...
the curse.
You can't stop me.
I'm doing it.
It's a shitty one!
Of course it is.
Just my luck.
At least we got a key out of it.
Shittiest consolation prize of all time.
Okay, maybe a secret room.
Ah, last bomb used.
See, if I had gone in here, I would have known.
That was just plain stupid.
Damn it!
Cellar 3!
We're gonna take damage and lose our...
devil chance, 100%.
Not taking damage in a game where everything is trying to damage you is kind of hard.
Oi!
Get by, Joe.
Hylai!
Ah,
get these guys down.
What did I get?
The fool.
Ooh, I can use that later, actually.
You know what?
Let's do that.
Let's go home.
Fuck you!
I lost my devils!
Ugh!
That's good.
I don't wanna re-roll that.
That's really solid, actually.
Man, the poop trinket is really nice.
Very helpful.
Jesus.
We got a tinted rock here.
Five keys, man.
Oh, not these guys.
I hate him so much.
Least favorite enemy in the entire game, I think.
Damn.
Another key.
Yeah, this shop has a lot of items all of a sudden.
Um, hold on a minute.
Let me see what I got here.
I kinda wanna buy the pill.
Okay.
I was hoping for a good pill.
Since I have the good pill, trinket thingy.
Oh, not quite a trinket, but an item.
Jesus Christ, please die!
Dude, stop with the keys!
Give me some bombs!
There's another tinted rock!
Why is it always like this?
Yeah, please kill this thing.
Okay.
Hey!
There we go!
Okay.
Come on, be good, be good.
We're gonna put it right here.
Ahh!
I mean, it's not that bad, I guess.
Uh, curse room is a possibility, but I'm kinda low on HP.
Nice!
Okay, our luck is turning.
I think it was over here, we saw a tinted rock somewhere.
Down here?
Yeah!
Massive!
Uh, okay, we're not done exploring, though.
I mean, we already lost the demon chance here, so who cares?
I'll just move on.
Now, this one's gonna be a little...
Actually, it's fine.
Oh, nice!
Ten coins.
Not bad.
No reward?
Weird.
Um...
I've made so many mistakes already, guys!
Is it over?
It may actually be over.
I was waiting for that.
Oh, god, am I gonna step in that?
More speed?
Dude, calm down with the speed, will ya?
I think I'm just gonna accept the fact that I'm not gonna get any, uh...
Oh, I could actually get in here.
It may actually be a waste not to do it, since I had such a low chance, right?
Let's do demons.
Wait, hold on.
Destroy this first.
I can't think when there's fires in there, even though they're not, like, bad fires.
Uh, blackheart damage...
This is actually such a good item.
This one...
No, absolutely not!
That one sucks ass!
Bonghole is what that sucks.
Not taking it.
Uh, I think I'm good.
I'm just gonna move on.
I'm gonna say no to that curse room, because now we have a one and a half buffer.
And it's- Oh, I forgot I could reroll!
I can still answer!
Haha!
Whoo-hoo!
Oh my god.
Well, there we go.
At least we're getting the blunders out of the way today.
We will never- We will not make any more mistakes this stream.
That was fucking cra- I just assumed the damn door was closing behind me!
Like it always does!
Fucking hell.
As soon as I jumped down, I saw the door, man.
I was like, wait a minute.
Shit!
Oh well.
It may actually be over.
Alright, nice.
That was a good room.
What is this guy in his little saucer?
Wait, where did he go?
Did he die?
I didn't kill him.
No reward again.
What is happening here?
Something fishy is going on.
Damn it!
Wait, we still have a bit of a buffer.
I like seeing all these poops.
That's good for me.
Okay.
Eh!
Uh...
I'll be back for- Why?
Hey!
Horrible item.
But I guess it is a way to get bombs if I need them.
And I don't have any right now.
So maybe just for that reason, it could be worth taking.
I just took damage, for fuck's sake.
The buffer dream is gone.
More keys, of course.
I don't have enough of those.
Okay.
Uh...
We're probably gonna have enough energy, actually, to reroll that once more if we want to.
Sick.
That was actually so masterfully done.
Oh!
We can use that against the boss.
If he spawns little guys, I guess.
Oh, this guy, I don't think he does.
He spawns into little two sub mini guys, and maybe those can be charmed.
Guess we'll find out.
Oh, you bastard!
Consume thy enemy, I don't even know what that is.
Grants an additional charged attack that creates a black ring around Isaac when released.
Hold on, grants an additional charge.
Alright, the ring deals...
Oh, oh wait, we've had this one before.
Why is this unknown to me?
Well, we figured out Pheromones does work on this guy when he spawns his little sub dudes.
That's not bad at all.
Oh, we're definitely taking that though, that is for sure.
Uh, school bag, yeah, definitely.
So, I wonder though, if I reroll now, are we going to have another deal right here?
Because this one was discounted, right?
I'll be back with more money.
Because if that's the case, we could really make use of that.
Yeah, this room is going to be impossible.
Nope, nevermind.
I thought we had the ring.
Down into the right.
Oh my God.
I'm too fast for my own good.
Oh, the D6 is ready.
I'm going to reroll this up here.
I don't like this.
Ugh!
So boring, I hate that item so much.
I'll be back for more.
Nice!
Oh, it actually does so much damage in the beginning though.
Very nice.
Okay, we're not done exploring.
And we have energy again.
Come on, this time though.
Please, please, please, please.
What is that bullshit?
That's horrible!
I swear, you know what, at this point I feel like the D6 is not even that good of an item.
You never get anything good when you reroll.
Never.
Oi, oi, oi.
Whoa!
Scary.
What's happening?
Oh, right.
My thing dealt damage because I took damage.
Okay, move on.
Oh wait, there was nothing else down here.
Fuck.
I have one bomb that I maybe could use for something.
You know what guys?
I think right here.
If not, we're gonna get mushrooms.
Shit!
Well, that was that bomb.
Worst treasure room of all time.
Absolute garbage items in there.
I think I'm gonna... try this.
It's not discounted.
Okay, well, at least we confirmed that.
Theory is dead.
Move on.
Catacombs.
Yeah, we're not doing great here.
Only two hearts is abysmal.
At this stage in the game, it's pretty much just over for me, but if I only have two hearts.
And there goes the Devil Chance.
Am I charging up faster?
I think I'm charging a little faster than I did before.
This one could actually be pretty good for me.
Other than that, I don't really want to do anything else in that room.
Batteries.
Ooh.
Could come in handy.
Could actually come in big handy.
Especially with all the keys we have.
Oh, no.
How I didn't take damage there, I don't understand.
D6 is ready.
Let's find a treasure room.
Fuck off!
I thought they all retracted, man.
Bullshit.
Another shit item?
There we go!
D6, best item in the game.
Best item.
But now I'm going to die because I have one HP, so it's going to suck real bad dying now.
I can't get to those.
Where's the boss even?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, let me think.
Yeah, we don't have any HP, this is bad.
Holy shit.
Huge healing, nice.
Sci-fly, do your thing.
I love you, Sci-fly.
Okay, he wants bombs?
No.
I do want to go in here, though.
Okay, this is actually huge.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Black candle!
Ooh, that's nice, I'm taking that.
Definitely taking that.
We can also heal up a little bit, or grab the heart.
Let me think.
Yeah, actually, protect my black heart a little longer, and this one's going to be a good pill, right?
We know that.
Nice.
Very nice.
Keep moving.
Here we go.
The holo!
I think we may have saved the run.
Wait a minute.
We have a problem.
Guys, we need one more charge on the D6.
This better be good.
Oh, never mind, nice.
Please spawn your little dudes.
Spawn them now.
Oh, wait, you're not that guy.
I thought you were someone else.
Head of Krampus, fires a brimstone laser attack.
Oh, man, I want to keep my... Wait, I can re-roll it.
I'm a... wait, I also have backpack!
Ooh, I'm going to re-roll this.
Oh!
I mean, it's still fine, I guess.
We can use both.
Yeah.
Okay, okay.
Sweet.
Not too shabby.
Didn't lose any HP during that either, so that's nice.
Let's go back and see what else we can do here.
I didn't mean to...
Actually, maybe we will give him some.
Okay.
Egg!
He was... Wait, wait, before I take that, this will heal me.
Wait, bomb explosion spawn a puddle.
Okay, yeah, no, actually take it now.
It's fine.
I'm sitting here thinking if I should go back to the curse room.
I don't think it's a good idea, because I finally have a buffer and we can use that in the next floor, right?
Yeah.
Then again, we haven't found any secret rooms.
Chances, though, are pretty slim.
Only two bombs?
Let's just move on.
Yeah.
We're moving.
The dank... depths.
Oh, wait, I should have taken a battery before I got in here, actually.
That would have been even better.
But it's okay.
This black ring is actually really helping.
Oh, no.
I let go of the button.
He's dead.
You're dead.
Nice.
Good.
Actually, take a look inside.
Uh...
All right.
Just die.
Ah, that was a bit too greedy on my part.
I should have just waited.
Ho-ho.
Well, the boss is here.
I think we do it when we have the buffer and we have a full d6.
Also, use this one, I forgot.
Here we go.
And go.
So, Haunt, it's double trouble.
I was a little premature with my ring.
Not bad, not bad.
Blue Cat, that's gonna take us to two out of three on Fun Guy.
Actually, not a bad idea.
Do we have a...
No demon.
But I actually like this.
I'm taking it.
Not re-rolling that.
Um... Yeah, let's keep moving.
Gotta find a treasure room, right?
What the... Oh, he jumped into me.
That little bastard.
This room was kinda nuts.
Charge it up.
Ha!
I... If I do the smart, like, here...
Beautiful.
Oh, no!
Okay, fine.
Okay, I got two of my bombs back, at least.
Not an entirely wasteful thing, then.
Uh, Mom?
Oh, spiders!
I was just looking for Mom's hand.
Here we go.
Oh, that's toxicity.
Uh, poison salt enemies.
I don't really like this.
Dead Eye, granted stacking damage, but ooh, I like that one more.
But let's just hold off, in case we get something better.
Lot of money.
Nothing to spend it on.
Wait, do we have batteries lying around?
Don't think so.
Ah!
Opened!
Use the monster manual.
PJs.
Wait, heals all... Did it say our hearts or blue hearts?
Did it grant four blue hearts or something?
What's it say?
Oh, I can't read it yet.
Weird that I can't read that during combat.
Maybe not to clutter the screen.
That makes sense.
Uh, heals all red hearts and four soul hearts.
Okay.
You know what this means, right?
It means we're gonna go step...
This is a stepping item.
Definitely.
Down, down, down.
Huh?
Oh, I got a shield.
You know what?
I'm actually a little scared.
If we accidentally trigger something, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna...
Pick this up.
And then go back.
I feel blessed.
Come on, get the shield away from me.
I'm actually a little too scared.
I'm gonna grab some...
No, one more.
Okay.
Let's go heal.
Boom.
Not bad, huh?
We got something out of that.
Oh, uh, what is that one?
I, I'm, I'm... shit.
Okay, check it out.
Don't mess, this needs to be precision now.
Precision.
Hold on.
I'm going into this room.
Hey, okay.
I think it's time to leave.
Twenty-one coins, though?
Ah, shop is not a shop.
It's a fake shop.
Alright, let's get out.
Dude, I hate the layout on these rooms.
You, you can't move anywhere.
It's just...
Crammed as hell.
No, this way.
I also gotta get this item in here.
Totally worth.
Okay, checklist before I go.
Uh, step, we can't actually, you know what, let's keep stepping.
I have so many blue hearts.
I didn't realize how, uh, how rich I was in that department.
Just a bit more.
We already did so much, right?
Okay, baby!
I'm glad I did it!
That's a wafer.
We're taking that one.
Good night, son.
Killed this little dude.
Okay, my damage is not that great.
It's okay, you know, but not much more than that.
Okay.
Also, uh, treasure room.
We have a full D6 now.
I just noticed.
Here we go.
Uh, wait a step.
Each missed shot has a chance to reset.
Uh, re-roll.
Fortune cookie!
Chance to drop a soul heart.
Okay.
Huh.
All right.
Uh, give me that one back.
Give me that one back.
Monster manual is still fine.
Yeah, whatever.
Let's go.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, it was a heart.
Okay.
I think we're done here.
Five bombs.
We could maybe look for a secret.
Actually, I think I see a good candidate area for it.
This looks good.
Let's see the bottom.
Also looks good.
Hells yeah!
How does he do it?
Now we move on.
Beautiful stuff here.
Whoo!
Let's go.
And now it's mom.
It's time for mom.
We have the fool.
Uh, can we... there.
Thank you.
Pills are good.
Nice.
Now I can't get over there, unfortunately.
Uh, use that.
This is a little funky.
Jesus.
Hey, how did I do it?
That's crazy.
Okay, that was not so good.
Don't take that card.
We don't need this.
We're gonna keep the fool.
Now we just need to focus on damage because we have sci-fi and wafer.
Charge it up.
D6 is getting charged as well.
Oh, wait a minute.
This one is, uh, Epikak!
Dude, hold on.
What is my range?
Ooh.
My range is really far, man.
But I have good survivability and I have wafer.
I think it's worth it.
This one also reduces the range.
I'm doing it.
Yeah, it's not that bad.
It's fine.
Now we cannot pick up range anymore.
No more range.
This is great.
Nice.
D6 is ready.
For action.
I need to find a boss now.
What is that one again?
Uh, may not... I mean, at this point.
We have money for it.
Kinda wanna get a pill.
Oh no.
Shit.
Now there's a battery in here we can potentially buy later for an extra re-roll.
Oh, let's also remove these now.
In fact, destroy all the rocks.
You never know what you're gonna find.
And of course, look for...
This is also the other bonus with this.
We can find all secrets.
Whoa!
Die-shirt!
Hold on a minute.
The hell?
Pill!
Hmm.
Okay, that's not too great, actually.
Maybe I'll take cards.
Judgment?
What is that one again?
Judgment.
Oh, right!
Okay.
Eh.
Don't really wanna do anything with you.
I could blow... I could blow you up.
Hey!
Okay.
Give me this card back.
We cannot leave this card out of our sight, by the way.
It's so important.
Nice.
Uh...
I could donate to this.
Let me check the shop again.
So this is the mom... I think we should start just buying and using the rest of the money we have.
To be honest.
Just give me that one.
Could also donate some money, but...
Monster Manuel?
Oh, that's so sad.
I can't get these.
That hurts, man.
Wait, did that spawn from a skull?
Oh my
god!
All these items I can't get.
It hurts.
Dude, destroying skulls is kinda...
good.
Uh... wait, wait, before we... no, no, we can do it now, because we're getting out anyway afterwards, so it's fine.
We just check.
The full check.
These takes check.
Okay, go!
Come on, mom!
Uh... just take the negative.
Whatever.
Oh!
Remember, we can re-roll!
But that's actually not bad!
It is bad, because we have so much damage anyway, this is not gonna affect me.
Re-roll.
Guppy's head.
And this one is... contract from below.
Ewwww!
I don't know, man.
Also, what's this?
Okay, nice.
Guppy's head.
So wait a minute.
I kinda wanna... here's the plan, okay?
I wanna take one of these, I wanna leave this room, go get the battery, come back, but I don't know if the room stays open.
I think it may close.
So that's why I'm gonna buy one of these items before I leave.
I'm taking this one.
Then we can take that one.
And then we go.
Ah, but wait, I can't come back.
I'm an idiot.
The question is, do I want this?
No, I don't want that actually.
I'm good.
Take me back.
Keep exploring.
Precision shots right there.
Oh, skulls.
Destroy them all.
Yeah, my range is too much.
Oh, that's a champion guy!
What do we get?
Nothing?
I kinda wanna do a speedrun as well.
Well, not in this run, of course, but maybe next one.
New card.
The stars.
Well, don't waste it here.
Hey, I can actually...
I can actually come back to the boss room and get out again.
But I don't know if the demon room is gonna be open now.
But we can try it, I just need a bit more battery first.
Wait, so I can't... No, I can't get over there.
Whoa, check this room out.
Wait, how am I gonna do this?
Oh, unbelievable.
Unbelievable.
The money that I can't get, unfortunately.
For you.
That's for you.
Okay.
Oh, that was fast.
Oh, god.
Frickin' worms!
Ibikak is kinda hard to control.
Oh, god.
Dagas removes curse and grants so hard?
Maybe.
I gotta try the stars thing first, though.
Can we get the last battery or charge?
I don't think we can, honestly.
Maybe we find a secret room.
So, wait, we found one secret room.
There's also a black heart.
Oh, that's the one I can't get to, right?
Oh, let's check the fight room.
Closed.
Damn.
How am I gonna get this last?
I mean, I could just keep destroying things.
So, where would it be?
Another fool!
Dude!
Alright.
Well, I'm not gonna lack for teleports here.
Maybe up here-ish?
You know what?
I'm gonna donate the rest of my money.
I really should have just done that instead of taking that bag.
Uh, maybe in here.
I will find this secret room.
Oh, god!
Not there.
Here?
There we go.
Finally.
Okay.
Mushroom time.
That means pills.
Hopefully.
How am I gonna get over there?
Can't even hit this guy.
God, I hate this range that you-I'm just gonna blow them up.
No!
Where are my pills at?
Okay, this one we should be able to hit.
Uh,
wow.
Nothing.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, we can get in here.
Holy shit!
We're gonna get the last battery here.
Can you please stand still?
I feel like my damage is not that good.
I forgot I had to circle.
Nice.
Tears up.
The stars.
Uh, you know what I'm gonna do?
Check this out.
I'm gonna optimize even more.
I'm gonna go grab the-also, we may as well use-no, I'm gonna save this actually.
I'm gonna grab the fool now.
Then we save the stars for the next floor.
The next floor?
Does that even have one of those rooms?
Ah, we'll find out.
Okay, here we go.
Let's see if this works.
Please be there.
Okay, well, we tried.
It was worth a shot.
I'm gonna grab the other card again.
Wait, we also have a card on the other side here.
What was that one?
Nah, two damage does nothing for me pretty much.
Not when I have 47, right?
The only thing that really matters now is tears.
That's my-that's gonna amplify my damage.
Okay, here we go.
We aligned stars.
Oh, we also have a rune we could pick up.
The one that removes a curse may actually be better.
Because I don't see when I'm gonna teleport anyway.
Yeah, let's just keep the dagas.
Here we go.
Gonna destroy these, of course.
Wow, nothing.
Okay.
I think we have a pretty good shot at this.
The virus...
You know what?
I don't want this, so I'm gonna re-roll it.
Horrible!
He thinks it's the worst item, dude.
Delga!
There were skulls in there as well.
I need flying.
Oh, wait, wait.
Don't mess this up.
Wait, I still can't...
Unless I'm smart about this.
Watch.
Aha!
Alright, not bad.
Bob's curse.
What is it with these fucking bombs?
There we go.
Pushed a little more.
Sick.
Without taking damage.
More spiders.
Pills!
Charms all enemies.
Oh, crap.
Okay, I guess we're in here now.
Whoo!
Look at that one.
Exciting.
Just more chests.
Hey, more tears is huge.
Wishbone, chance when taking damage to destroy the trinket and spot an item.
You know what?
At this point, why not?
I think I've definitely used the poop...
to its fullest extent.
Okay, nothing.
Kill him!
I will destroy the rocks.
If I can.
Okay, whatever.
I still feel like my attack speed is very low.
Boomerang.
Oh, I forgot to use this.
I could re-roll here.
It's almost the effects of most cards.
Interesting, if I get a really good card.
I could donate, but let's wait.
We're not going to enter that yet, of course.
Whoops.
I forgot that we have to look for secrets.
Two of hearts, and another two of hearts.
Cool.
Wait!
I can't get in there!
Oh well.
That's sad.
I need to find secrets.
Oh, re-roll this!
Quintz, the first five enemies killed in each room will spawn a random friendly baby familiar.
Uhh...
Let me think.
Is that a good item for what I'm doing?
I don't... maybe.
I'll come back.
I don't... Oh, what's with this rock?
Look at these rocks, they look weird.
They're like holes.
They're holes in them.
Like Swiss cheese.
Doesn't mean anything.
How is that?
Oh yeah, right.
Dude, I love that it also hits the enemies.
Oh, what's this?
Damage?
No, no, this is bad for me.
I'm gonna gamble.
My little unicorn!
Goddammit.
Grant's invincibility and bonus speed.
That's very meh.
Oh, no, no, I want that one.
Maybe I'll reroll it if I get enough battery.
We'll see if we can get enough.
I doubt it, though.
We just can't get any more range.
Oh, flight!
Umm... You know what, I'm gonna use this here.
And grab this one.
There was a room where I needed flight for something here.
Where are the secret room?
I could get that chest with flight, but it may not be worth it yet.
I really frickin' hate the range thing with the Ibi-Kak.
It is so annoying.
I don't even want to destroy the rest.
Maybe check for secrets.
I almost have full battery again.
Could fly in here.
Dude, have I not checked everywhere?
I'm so confused!
No, never mind, what the fuck, there it is.
I'm gonna donate all my money here.
Shit.
Okay, well, I didn't lie, I'm gonna donate all my money here.
Unless I want some of this.
Nice!
It broke at one coin left, that's crazy.
I think we're done!
Oh, wait, I see a blue heart?
Is that one of those I couldn't pick up for some reason?
Yeah, okay.
Let's use the Hank, man.
Not very useful.
I think we're good.
Let's go.
I think this one's gonna be tough, guys.
Ibi-Kak is kinda hard to use.
I need pyromaniac, I need the healing thing.
Oh, man.
I need a bit more mana.
The stars?
And this is, what is that?
Good.
Let's go re-roll this.
Tiny planet.
No!
The D6, man.
Terrible.
Shit!
It's always blue balls with that item, you know?
Yeah.
Let's grab that card.
No, do we want the stars here?
It's not gonna help us with anything, right?
This is better.
If we get to three hearts, we can use it and fully heal on red.
We need precision with the Ibi-Kak.
I like that they get poisoned from this, so they die right after, you know?
I mean, this room just wants to get destroyed.
Nothing.
I've gotten so many keys on this run.
I'm not done exploring.
Also, this is not gonna be super useful though, because there's only every one of these floors, right?
So it's gonna go away again.
Monster manual.
I guess we'll see.
Take me up.
Yeah, now it's gone again.
Why did I take damage?
What did I do?
Nothing.
Not even a blue heart.
I'm gonna keep exploring.
The best part about sci-fi?
I don't have to worry about inanimate objects.
My worst nemesis.
Okay, just go.
Take me.
I think this is the last time I used the monster manual before we get to the boss.
Jesus Christ!
What a horrible room.
Is that a friend?
Oh, it is.
Jesus Christ!
I'm not getting those, am I?
I'm losing all my buffers here.
Shit!
Tears up though.
Fuck, I could have rerolled that.
But I guess it's fine.
It's a decent item.
Yeah, I'm actually fine.
I think he's good.
Take me!
Fuck his life.
I will never pray with you, Mom.
Never.
I'm back to re-roll it!
Ha!
Still sucks ass.
That's like five re-rolls so far.
Ace of clubs.
Wait, what?
Transform all pickups, chests, trinkets and enemies into bombs?
What?
No, no thanks.
Not right now.
I'm not feeling it.
Sounds a little too crazy.
Let's go.
Whatever.
He wants keys?
Oh, I've got keys for your ass.
I've been waiting the whole run for this.
Oh shit.
Okay.
Oh, can we get this out of here?
Get this ch- No!
I'm an idiot.
We will never speak of this?
Why is this guy so tanky?
Dude, will you die?
What the fuck?
Thank you.
Took forever.
What is that?
Magic fingers?
No.
No thanks.
Guys, I think Ipecac may have actually fucked me in this run.
Like, it's good, but it's just not good enough.
I think I'm gonna die with- because of Ipecac.
I was actually hesitant.
Like, the damage is not that good, look.
Huh?
What just happened?
Whatever.
Take me.
Uh...
Interesting room.
Blow them up.
Something.
Thing's never gonna die.
Yeah,
I don't understand what's going on there.
Oh wait, is that because- Whoa!
Hold on a minute now!
Now it got a little interesting.
This is gonna be dangerous to use.
It's gonna be really dangerous to use.
Ugh.
Wait, bombs fired te- Yo!
Actually not bad, check this out.
Wait, that doesn't sh- fire shots or what?
Is it only- oh, is it only these bombs?
Oh, that's- that's scary in itself right there.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah, I think we may be cooked.
I think it's ogre.
What's this?
Mom's purse, allows the trinkets to be held at the time.
I don't have any trinkets, man.
Oh wait, I have more now.
Missing page.
Okay, check it out.
This is gonna be the self-suicide strategy.
I'm gonna go brrrrhhhhhh with the bombs, and every time I take damage we're gonna deal 120 damage.
Well, 5% chance of it, at least.
Necromonicon, Blackhearts, and Drybab, you also do this increased damage, whatever.
Sure...
Go to bed.
We are so cooked.
The Ipikat is gonna bite me in my loins.
Also, wait a minute, we can't
even...
Wait, what if I don't find a key?
What, then?
Then I just can't do that?
You gotta be kidding me.
Here we go, here we go.
Dukma!
What's up, Dukma?
Jesus Christ.
Okay, good.
This is scary, man.
Okay, he's dead at least.
This is gonna be bad, guys.
It's gonna be bad!
Okay, here we go.
Oh crap.
Just stay at range.
No reason to overdo it.
Okay, okay, okay.
He's gonna appear from the left now?
No, right, okay.
You're dead, son.
Okay, I think we may be able to do this, guys.
I'm feeling good about this.
Also, monster manual, what the hell?
Okay, okay.
Nice.
I'm taking too much damage.
Also, I think my two of hearts is not gonna work while I'm flying here.
That's kind of bad.
Okay, okay.
Here we go.
Wait, that doesn't hit him?
Oh, it's because we didn't start yet.
Oh my god.
What the hell is that?
Shit.
Two of hearts did nothing.
Oh my god.
Oh boy.
Options has appeared in the basement.
We can finally change the resolution.
No more pixelated gameplay.
Guys, that was awesome.
And you know what?
Win streak four.
I'm gonna take a quick break, guys.
I need to take a piss real bad.
I'll see you in a bit.
All right.
Let's keep it going, huh?
This is a great streak we're on.
Uh, what do I want to play?
I kind of want to do Eden.
I already have so many marks on Eden.
We can do... Bethany.
Let's do Bethany again.
That was actually so nice last time.
I like it.
Three red hearts.
We got a treasure room right here.
Amazing.
What is that?
Oh, wait.
2020.
That's pretty much like like the book one.
Bookworm.
But better.
And less damage.
But you know, at least we fire two tiers.
So it's kind of but with less damage.
You know what I mean.
Tinted rock spotted.
I think I should just be doing this, honestly.
The earlier the better.
Now I understand how this character works.
Shit.
Well, at least I didn't take damage from that.
Actually, maybe the better idea is to save these charges for the next floor.
You know, because that's when you want the buffer and you can see these flies as or wisps as buffers, right?
What the hell?
Stop that.
Stop.
Let me see.
Yeah.
There's options.
That's a really good one, man.
I could destroy this if I get a bomb.
I didn't mean to fucking donate my coin.
That was a mistake.
Yeah.
How are you supposed to avoid that?
It is impossible.
I couldn't do anything there.
That's just fucked by RNG or something.
Uh, I should have used my active before I cleared this room.
Use it now.
Famine.
Man, he spawns a lot and fast.
What the hell?
Nice.
Oh, I fucking hate this item.
It is so bad.
Honestly, like this one and the bandage one or whatever, it's just the worst items.
I hate them so much.
I'm dead.
Well, it was fun.
Great, great run.
Love it.
You can't do anything against like you can't do anything.
I am just fucked by RNG twice with bombs in that run.
Great.
Lovely.
That was so much fun.
That was fucking stupid.
Unbelievable.
To have it all end like that is just insane to me.
Honestly, just... Wow, that just tilted me so much.
That just felt like such bullshit, like that entire run.
In five minutes, I've experienced more bullshit than I have in like the last 10 hours of this game.
Crazy.
Insanity.
What's that?
Yeah, I mean, sure.
Let's see what we get.
Taurus.
This is the one where you reach a maximum speed.
I really don't like this item very much.
Honestly, just kill me.
I don't...
New run.
No, thanks.
We already have a shitty streak anyway.
Who cares?
You know what?
Just fucking step yourself to death.
That fly just saved me.
I mean, at the beginning of a run, you have nothing to lose anyway, right?
So, may as well just step.
That's a shitty-ass item.
So, it's like guaranteed now.
There's always six items in the shop, I think.
Okay.
Maybe we can have there be even more.
See, why did that guy just explode?
Maybe they're like on a timer.
Some of them.
Oh yeah, right.
That's how blue hearts work here.
Oh, maybe the guy walked into flames before.
That's probably what that was.
Jira.
Wait, that's gonna... If I do that in the shop, I can just pick them up for free, right?
Also, I have two bombs in case I need to do something with it.
Uh, wait, that's not the shop.
I'm an idiot.
Shop is over here.
Nice.
Magician.
I'm gonna take this.
I'm gonna do it again.
Okay, not bad.
Okay, right here.
Yep.
I'm happy.
Oh no, my fly.
Oh, he's too fast for me.
Almost wanted to activate Magician there.
What the hell, man?
I need cheese configuration.
Stay away from me.
There we go, cheese.
Almost.
Ah, whatever.
Okay, I have four coins.
I mean, uh, keys here.
I can definitely just do this.
Ooh.
Nice.
By the way, I'm at half a heart here.
Crazy.
Uh, nothing.
I want a bomb.
This is dangerous.
Dude, I'm focusing so much right now.
Okay, good.
Still no hearts.
What the hell?
I need healing.
15 coins.
Ah, boy, this one shoots it back.
But it's actually not bad.
I think I want this.
Yeah, I mean, the range is good still.
And I don't care that they come back here.
I'm fine with that.
Dude, nothing?
Not even a single heart?
Oh, fuckers spawned a centimeter away from me.
Come on.
Terrible.
Yeah, whatever.
Go big or go home, right?
This will just restart if we die.
Okay, nothing.
Money, that's good.
Wow, that's really good.
That is insane.
I'm going to take that later.
Another coin.
That's 18 already.
Oh, yeah, we're going to die.
This is the end.
Wait, how did that guy down there?
There was no fire to run into.
Huh.
Oh, yeah, they do just kind of explode.
It seems.
Some of them, at least.
Nice.
Is this guy going to explode?
Yeah, look at that.
I think it's when I get within a certain range.
Then it starts.
Mystery solved.
Monster manual.
How's that going to work with my active?
Let's see.
One in a wisp, 4 HP, 3 damage, random tier effects.
Ooh, don't like that.
Okay.
18 coins, though, it's crazy.
Pay to play is actually kind of good.
I'm taking that.
I'm also going to take the buffer, but not yet.
We're going to wait until we've beaten the boss.
So that's just permanent.
I can have this weird effect with the monster manual.
Or it's just because I randomly spawned this.
It's RNG, right?
What I get.
Oh, no, he's down there.
Okay, I see.
Oh, yeah, he's down in the corner.
I think we're good.
Good start.
Kind of weird, though, the way that works.
All right, get rid of this poop.
Okay, not bad.
Shot speed and chance of planetariums.
Yeah, I mean, those things are just ultra rare.
So getting a higher chance for that is good.
Fool.
Nice.
Okay, go back now.
We have a couple things to do.
I'm going to take this.
Wait, why is that attached to the rightmost heart?
Isn't that weird?
Maybe it's always the rightmost red heart that I have.
So no matter what other hearts I have, it's almost the rightmost red one.
That was a hard sentence to say.
Go!
Okay.
Oh, wait, I don't get a... Oh, I don't get a buffer from this, of course.
That's not how she works.
Wait, how am I going to do this?
That's awkward.
I mean, this works.
It's going to take a while, but it is what it is.
I need more of these wisps.
That's a lot.
Uh, go north.
The magician.
I think I need to hold on to the fool, though, if I want to go home.
But I can use this on this floor.
Okay, fully charged, finally.
Do we get a second?
Does that mean we do two of these?
Oh, nice.
Very nice.
That's really cool, actually.
The hourglass.
So wait, how does this work now?
Does it just replace the manual?
Slows all enemies when killed.
That's kind of interesting.
It shoots green thingies now.
I don't know if I... I mean, if I fight another book, we're gonna have three out of three already.
So that's nice.
I think I'll try this for a bit.
See how it works.
But I would need to get hit, right?
The good thing is, it's only two charges on this one.
So I get to use it much more often.
Wait, what does it actually do when using it?
Oh, it just slows them for eight seconds, okay.
So every second room, I'm gonna get another charge.
Yeah.
What the heck is that?
Add a bastard box.
Whoa, that has a lot of charges.
The box is consumed to spawn two random angel room pedestal items and three soul hearts.
If a devadil has been taken, spawns one angel room item and two soul hearts instead.
Starts depleted and can only be charged by picking up soul hearts and black cards.
Oh, shit, okay.
Hearts consumed to charge the box are not added to Isaac's health meter.
Oh, okay.
I mean, it's not added to me anyway.
So that's actually not bad.
Oh, I think I understand how this works now.
So when it says up to eight metal wisps, it means I spawn eight at once when I use this.
Or maybe it's the max.
I'm not sure.
Could be a couple of things, I guess.
Well, we're gonna do this for sure.
Sounds awesome.
Can I not transfer my current blue hearts I have stockpiled somehow?
That's too bad.
Oh, I keep this one.
No, no, take this one and do the boss now.
Hold on, we have a hundred percent angel chance.
Oh, yeah, I guess this is just what this character has.
Okay, here we go.
Magician.
Magic.
That's actually just bullshit.
I was not standing on that.
I ran near the edge, dude.
Are you fucking kidding me, man?
I was visually not on the fucking creep.
That sucks ass.
I was like, oh, I can definitely just run around that.
God, it feels terrible.
Oh, wait a minute now.
We have two charges that are green, but we have blue charges that is filling up as well.
So, wait, we get to use this more than once then or what?
Wait a minute.
Is that right?
It says it's consumed, but is it consumed while I have it sort of linked up with my book?
That's the question.
There we go.
Blackheart is what we need for this.
Nice.
It gets charged.
I can't get over that creep just now, like that.
Jesus.
Uh, wait, wait, wait.
Go in here.
Yeah, just gamble.
Nice.
Good start.
Okay, that's actually kind of nice.
So, wait, how does that work?
Wisp spawn based on item payout?
Wait, what?
Oh, so if I don't get anything?
Oh, I see.
So, whatever.
If I get a red heart, I get a red wisp thingy.
This is actually kind of really good.
Okay, thanks.
Oh, you know what it could do.
I could do this.
I'm not done gambling.
Damn.
Nice.
Take this one again.
Pills.
Amnesia.
It's too bad.
Oh, let's not waste our flies here.
Oh, what was that?
Damn.
I mean, that's too late now.
Okay.
I'm going to take this back.
Honestly, this is getting a little crazy.
Not even sure what's happening here.
This is so funky.
Yeah, I didn't want any of this anyway.
Well, I'm going to be ready for the next floor.
Let's go.
I have a lot of different flies or wisps on me now.
I keep calling them flies.
Why not?
Huh?
Oh, I need keys for, I mean, coins.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Kind of want to go in there.
Maybe I'll do more stepping.
I want to find the boss first.
The best part about these wisps is that they have a lot of pushback.
Oh, man.
I want that.
No.
Can't get it.
This is so weird.
This character is actually kind of nuts because do they have to make it like an interaction with every single other active item in the game?
I almost can't believe that.
That's nuts.
I'm imagining a million different builds with this.
Wait, what is spawning the bombs?
Is it me?
How's it happening?
Yeah, the bomb just spawned near the corners of the...
Fucking...
What just happened to the sound there?
What the fuck is that?
I'm so confused.
I think I've seen that before, but I just don't know what it is.
Oh, terrible item.
Whatever.
Yeah, I'm spawning bombs just randomly here.
It's got to be one of my wisps.
Boss, I think we should do it.
Let's try not to take damage here.
It's going to be so difficult.
It's going to spawn another piece of shit now.
Oh, I'm losing all my guys.
My army's dissipating.
Shit.
No!
We have a choice.
Eyedrops or free lemonade.
I mean, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm curious to see how this is gonna...
...wish beliefs creep.
I think I want tears.
I just want, I need damage.
I need, I need to improve my DPS.
I'm not done here.
Can't even get to that.
So we have three hearts, two hearts right now.
Definitely doing curse room.
Curse room.
And then we leave.
Watch this.
Damn!
Horrible curse room.
Okay, right here, though.
Duh, I should have checked this room first.
I'm too lazy, man!
Too lazy for that.
No idea where the other one could be.
All right, let's go.
Okay, uh, we're gonna lose this angel chance.
We got no buffer.
Wait, how are these bombs spawning?
Is it one of these?
Is this one?
I have no clue how these bombs are spawning.
I can't run into that chest.
Not yet.
Okay.
I can't wait to charge this active.
Great.
We will never see an angel.
Never.
And the main gameplay mechanic of this character has kind of been...
neglected because of this active, you know?
Can't wait to see how it turns out, though.
I feel like I'm just uninstalling the game right now.
Okay, run is over!
Kill me.
I don't even want to play this run, dude.
No thanks.
Next one.
Absolute dogshit.
This is called optimized gameplay right here.
See, that was better.
We got two coins out of it.
Much better.
This is how you get a good start.
Come here.
Okay, so much HP.
Damn.
Don't do it.
Kamikaze.
Explode.
Warning.
Damages Isaac too.
Explosive tears.
That's interesting.
Wait, what?
Hold on.
Huh?
So wait, my tears explode or...
No, they don't.
Unless it's meant for my wisps.
Ah, I see.
Okay.
That's kind of neat, actually.
Yo, imagine getting this on...
I was about to say Magdalene, but then it doesn't matter, right?
Because we're not playing this character anymore.
It's a very fun mechanic.
We get to destroy rocks with it?
Whoa, that is really good.
I didn't think that would work.
Even better.
Oh yeah, let me in.
A Bible.
Wait, what did that do again?
Homing tears.
But only for my wisps.
Unfortunately.
We don't know what that pill is.
I think I may just get this.
It's all about healing.
And exploding.
Come here.
Dude, this is a really fun interaction there.
Okay.
We're gonna bomb ourselves on the boss.
Bandage.
Yeah!
Oh, that's really good.
That's really good.
We have a synergy going now.
That's really fun.
We get money as well.
Can we look for secrets with this?
Let's destroy walls as well, because then it's even better.
Also, am I gonna take damage from these explosions?
The mini explosions.
Let's see.
Wait, I can't really hit myself with it, it seems.
Unless I catch up to it?
Yeah, it's impossible.
Don't want to buy anything here, actually.
Wait, does that actually hit the wall?
You may need to be at the right distance here.
What about here?
Okay.
Oh, you can't hit yourself with it!
Evil charm!
Grants limited immunity to enemy creep and fireplaces, allowing Isaac to touch them for up to one second.
That's awesome!
Good start!
Can I destroy little dudes with this?
I can!
With a good aim, I can.
But what about the other secret rooms?
The thing is, I don't know if my shot is actually hitting it correctly, you know?
Like, if I overshoot the wall, it's still gonna work, kind of.
That's where I'm at.
Oh!
Here we go!
You want keys?
You're not getting it.
I will blow you guys up, though.
I think I'm good.
Let's go.
You know what we need now?
Imagine if we get pyromaniac now, or whatever the one is called that heals me when I bomb.
Oh!
Now that sounds awesome.
Now, the question is, am I gonna lose my angel status if I bomb myself?
Probably yes.
Can I have to fire booger tears?
Though, shooting two at a time now, it's really nice.
Gotta destroy them all.
What the hell is that?
Swallow a penny!
Spawns a coin each time I...
Dude, we're gonna spawn things every time we take damage.
This is the build for that.
Exciting.
Dang it.
Oh yeah, we lost the angel chance.
Again!
Feels good.
Are you fucking kidding me, man?
What?!
This room!
Insanity!
Let's go here.
Fine!
More gambling.
Uh...
No.
I think I'm just gonna do this one.
Then again, we haven't found a shop yet.
Actually, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
We need to see.
What if there's something omega good in the shop, right?
Careful now.
No!
Okay, come here.
I gotta have one of these on me.
Okay.
Hey, wait, wait, wait, what?!
How's this gonna work?
X10 Middlewisp spawns a golden troll bomb on death.
Wait, on death?
How's that gonna help me if I'm dead anyway?
Consume to spawn a massive shockwave.
And so I should all break up all of these in the room.
Shockwave reverberates once through every room entered for the remainder of the floor.
Kinda wanna save this for like the very, very last, you know?
But, I mean, may as well activate it now and then use the other one.
Okay, uh, get to- Oh, wait, wait.
Is my kamikaze gonna get swapped then?
Because this is gonna destroy this thing here.
Hold on a minute.
I need to think about this.
Okay, let's try it.
Okay, it's not gonna swap the kamikaze.
That's good.
Spider-man!
And treasure-man.
I don't- give me that.
Wait, are these all- What are these flies?
Or wisps?
Where did they come from?
I'm so confused- Oh!
Oh, right.
Everything explodes.
Okay, we got secrets.
Sick.
Not bad.
Uh, we can maybe do some funny stuff here, actually.
Wow!
Jesus.
Sorry!
Take it!
There's golden bombs here, somehow.
This is weird.
I wanna see it explode on him.
Okay, let's do damage.
Wait, am I spawning these bombs?
Or is he spawning them?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Maybe that's from the interaction.
So yeah!
God damn, I'm leaving.
That's crazy.
Wait, am I flying?
Why am I flying?
Oh, that's why.
What's this?
Nice.
Keep bombing the shit out of every room.
I like the mega bomb.
The mega bomb is good.
Uh, where's the last secret?
Oh wait, we already found them, right?
Yeah, we found them already.
Okay!
Let's move.
Wait, there's actually something I wanna do.
Let's go in here as well.
Load them up.
Nice!
We are very rich now.
Ready for the next shot.
Okay.
It does seem like it's just one-shotting everything when you use that bomb, right?
I wonder if that works on the later bosses, too.
Wait, before I go.
We're gonna do this.
Oh, shit.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, okay.
All right.
Okay then.
I'm gonna keep bombing.
That's cool.
More money for me.
Why are we spawning money?
Oh yeah, right.
Because when I take damage, I get money.
This is a very unique interaction.
We have going on here.
Jesus.
I think we're good.
Okay.
Moving on.
We're gonna be shooting a lot of bombs now.
Here we go.
Holy carbon bombing.
Wow, doesn't even do that much damage.
I mean, it... you know?
Speed down.
Nice!
More health is good and we want red health, by the way.
Red health is the best thing for me right now.
Stop with the money already.
Whoa!
Okay, not too bad.
Oh, I love it.
Let's see.
Lots of question marks.
Black cat.
Ooh, that's nice.
Curse is gone.
We can see what we buy now.
Volts is... I'm really feeling that, honestly.
But who knows?
Maybe we get an item later that we want to use instead.
I doubt it though, but you know.
Hmm.
What about a card?
Oh, let's get a pill.
Oh, shit!
Health up!
Fuck yeah!
Let's just buy some HP.
Get this one.
The very nice.
And this one.
I'm good!
This is a very unique run, guys.
Very exciting.
Ah, wait, wait, wait.
Yeah, whatever.
Less speed.
Oh, wait, there's two... two pills.
Infested.
I look so silly, the character.
Oh,
yeah, I can fly now.
I gotta remember that.
I love the carpet bombing.
Epiphora.
Shooting continuously in one direction increases fire rate.
That's very mid, but I'll take it.
Why not?
No, I like my current one, actually.
But I guess I'll take it just to spawn the heart.
Oh, shit.
Wait, why didn't it spawn the heart?
Blackheart?
Oh, I guess it got put into my pool.
Damn!
Okay.
Choop.
I'm gonna blow myself up.
Dude, blow myself up does a lot of damage.
That boss just got pretty much one shot.
That's crazy.
Cheers.
You got angels, crown of light.
Ah, taking damage removes the effect.
This is pretty much anti-me right now.
But as long as I can stay up high, then maybe...
Okay.
It doesn't work on my bombs that I shoot, though.
Not... Take it now, otherwise this door will close properly.
I think... You know what?
Let's just go.
Let's go, man.
Let's not risk that eternal heart.
What's that?
Damn.
Even more every time I take damage.
It's not triggered from demon beggars or blood, and that is funny.
Part of me wants to take it just for fun.
No, that's stupid.
It's stupid.
Wait, I thought it was a fucking card!
I'm an idiot.
I can't get rid of it now.
Well, this is my life.
I thought I could take it back.
Damn.
Well, this is gonna be interesting.
That's all I'm saying.
Yeah, the bombs are definitely my main source of damage right now.
Uh, damage, speed, okay.
Better than that.
Show me a shot.
I kind of don't like this shot.
What am I gonna get?
Wait a minute.
Two cards at once, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
I get to have this one and that one.
You know what?
I'm gonna buy a key as well.
Good.
I needed more keys for the next floor.
And, oh, wow.
All right, I'm gonna donate the rest.
We're gonna find more money.
Yes, we'll do it.
A lot of luck just gained and some angel.
Oh, we get to destroy everything with this.
This is really powerful.
Duplicate all chests and pickups.
Nice.
I get to hold both of these.
I think I want this instead.
No, no, actually give me the lovers.
Lovers are good because I can get myself up to full health and get the crown effect and I can damage myself with the bombs and then, you know, yada, yada, yada.
So on and so forth.
Lived happily ever after.
Open.
Oh, what about here?
There we go.
More money my way.
What the hell is that?
A walnut?
Being hit by an explosion has a chance to destroy the trinket and spawn.
Wow, that's funny.
May as well do that now.
Yeah, see, this is the problem now.
Those bombs are not going to be fun.
Cancer.
That's actually not that good for me.
I want this instead.
Hmm,
head this way.
Man, that's scary.
Arcade.
Okay, so this guy's going to give me battery, which is useless.
I could donate a bunch of HP, get more money.
Hell yeah.
Oh, sick.
Very nice.
Let's get something good out of this one.
We need Wafer.
Wafer with this build is going to be nuts.
Also, what am I going to do with my 19 blue hearts?
I guess at some point, maybe I'll have to switch out my active.
Teleport to the boss room.
I mean, we could... why not?
Bring it on then.
Shit!
Oh, he's friendly.
Explode them all.
Mom's coin purse.
Random pills are going to be cards though, right?
Yeah.
Dagas.
Kind of like Dagas.
Okay, homing shots.
I wonder if the homing shots are going to apply to my wisps as well.
Okay, the rest of the cards are not super exciting.
I'm in danger.
We're not done.
So many cards.
What's up, dude?
No!
More secrets.
One more secret room somewhere.
My tears are actually doing pretty good damage as well.
Like that alone is doing work right now.
So what we can do here is this.
Oh my gosh!
Haha!
Scary.
We can go down here.
Okay.
I mean, I'm here to donate.
I can just hover above him and it'll automatically do it.
Give me like an item.
Cupice!
Okay.
Little chubby.
Not a big fan of that one.
Somehow I didn't lose any of my wisps there.
Okay.
I need to keep a teleport card on me as well.
Sweet.
Yeah, just add it to my collection.
With all these cards on the map, there's got to be one somewhere, right?
And I can also donate a bunch of... Oh no, I can't.
This is the one that spawns two red hearts.
Tear drop charm.
Increase the chance of lock base shots to be fired?
Do I have any of that stuff?
Uh, this one.
Maybe.
No.
Ready to negative effects.
Yeah, I don't know.
Keep giving it money.
Bible tract.
Tonsil.
Nah, I'm just gonna leave.
Maybe blow everything up here.
Nice.
I think we're good to go.
What a crazy floor this was.
Uh, what was that one?
Cancer.
Well,
I guess if I want to stop collecting coins now, I could do it.
But my main damage is going to be from these bombs.
So it's actually bad for me.
This is not a teleport or one of these teleports.
This one.
We got to grab that.
And Dagaz is the shitty one, right?
Let me see here.
Oh, I don't know.
I kind of want to... Yeah, let's change Dagaz.
Ah, but wait, the Emperor.
That teleport is not going to be helpful anyway.
Because it's going to take me back to the boss room.
Right?
We'll just confirm.
Yeah.
God damn it.
Why do you always realize that, like, last millisecond, you know?
Also, this is not the mom floor.
Next one.
There's so many
bombs everywhere.
What's that?
Varicose veins?
Is that an active?
Oh, oh, hey!
Sick.
I like that.
Oh, we can also destroy these.
We're getting all the effects that activate on taking damage in this run.
The
shop here is going to be interesting.
We got 15 coins.
This one was what?
Recharges?
Nah.
We got to buy these cards.
Another Emperor?
Wait, what?
How did I...
Okay, I don't know how to change that.
Give me that.
We got two emperors.
What's that one?
The Hankman?
Boo.
I guess we'll take this then.
Shit.
Give me that.
Okay.
We know where the boss is, but we need to find the teleport.
Opened up for some reason?
Oh no, that's not the one that opened.
But you know what?
I could actually do this here.
Ah, but we don't have wafers.
This is going to be a full heart every time.
Let me think about it.
It is so awesome just shooting bombs like this.
This is like my version of Ipikak.
This is Ipikak version two.
Reveals the map.
No.
The world.
Come on, give me a teleport.
Maybe we can find a teleport in one of these secret rooms.
Aha!
I can just enter like that?
In the middle of combat?
Oh, you're up there.
Not bad.
So comfortable destroying these with these bombs.
29 coins again.
We are just... Hold on.
Everything is a payable item.
Where is it?
No, that's not what I got this run.
I don't know why I'm getting so much money.
Also, what was this one?
Limited immunity to enemy creep.
It doesn't matter.
We fly anyway.
I'm so overwhelmed right now.
We may have to adjust the goals of this run here, guys.
Home is not happening.
That's a lot of hands.
Add it to the collection.
Shit!
You know what?
We actually do have a... There's a gambling machine.
I'm gonna check it out again.
Here and then left.
Wait, no, that's not a gambling machine.
I'm an idiot.
I could buy... What about this one?
Chance at the start of each new room to summon a permanently...
I mean, yeah, okay, why not?
I thought this wasn't active for some reason.
I mean, I may as well buy this as well.
No, that doesn't matter, actually.
Teleport to the boss room.
Boo.
This one's also teleport, right?
Yeah.
I can donate.
No.
Keep it.
Keep it for now.
Well, shit.
We can't go back then.
It is what it is.
Yeah.
Okay.
What I can do, though, is heal up a little bit here after I spawn a couple more of these guys.
Oh, up here.
Yeah, there we go.
Let's go.
I'm gonna do this, take that, and go.
Oh, wait, this is... Oh, wait, it's not mom yet.
It's next one.
Or floor.
Oh, hell yeah.
Looks like home's back on the menu, boys.
Placenta.
Oh, that's so good for me.
Placenta is amazing for me.
Now we just need wafer and everything is good.
Now it's mom.
Mom, mom, mom, mom.
Let's find a teleport.
I have... Yeah, this way.
This really just does feel like the better Ibikak.
Ha ha, nice healing.
I gotta be careful walking backwards when I shoot, because I can actually hit myself with the bombs.
In that case, I want to explore this room first down here.
You can even open these with the explosions.
Uh, what?
It's a chance of finding red heart.
That's actually even better for me, I think, than what I have.
I think it's about time we stop using the swallow penny anyway.
Yeah, why not?
I'm gonna go south here.
What was that?
Something appears.
I don't know what appears.
Jira.
Oh, I have two of hearts.
We don't need the hangman.
A fat bat... Oh, it's the poggo thing.
I see what it is.
Let's see what we get.
Uh, quintet thingy.
Quints.
Okay, whatever.
Why not?
Not bad.
Oh, checked it out.
I got 29 blue hearts ready and lined up here.
And this appears.
Oh, the four!
We got it, baby!
Fuck yeah.
Very nice.
Took long enough.
Also, how have I not lost my eternal heart so far?
I was ready.
I already accepted losing that, like ages ago, but somehow we haven't lost it yet.
Now we're done in here.
Oh, there goes.
Ghost baby.
Even more money.
Let's go restock on some explosive wisps.
Let me do that here, actually.
Stay away from me.
Okay, now we're done, though.
The Hierophants.
Sure added to the collection.
Wait, this guy wants hearts!
Damn right!
You can have some.
I can donate a lot to you.
Gympie.
Soulheart.
Oh, chance to drop a half red heart when killing an enemy.
That's very nice, too.
That's actually even better.
Okay, let's go.
I'm gonna do so much damage here.
Damn, she died fast!
Holy shit.
No angels, unfortunately.
Okay, are we ready?
I need to prepare myself a little bit more, actually.
What about this room up here?
Oh, shit, we haven't been here.
What's happening?
Okay, we're done.
We are fully loaded up now.
All right, let's go.
We're gonna heal up the last heart here.
Maybe grab an extra card before we leave.
Not the worst idea.
What's that one?
Hankman is useless.
That's pretty good.
We like that one.
Let's go.
If I can find the way back.
It's, I think, down here?
Somewhere?
Wait, no, no, definitely not down here.
Wait, where the hell?
Also, let's destroy this.
It's got a beard.
Oh, here it is.
Okay, let's do it.
Here we go.
Oh yeah, imagine pyromaniac.
Imagine that, or wafer.
That's like the cherry on top right now.
Uh, we still got people here?
Destroy these skulls.
I kind of want to find another active.
We got 54 coins for the shop.
Nice.
Wiggle worm.
Wait, tears travel in a wave-like pattern.
Let me see that.
And they're spectral, right?
But I mean, it doesn't really matter.
I think I want this instead.
Remind me exactly what it does.
Come on, show me the... Okay, thank you.
Chance to add an additional red heart.
Now, yeah, during boss fights, it's not gonna matter too much.
But it is nice to have just the extra hearts, I guess, for now.
We can donate.
Probably not gonna... Actually, it doesn't matter.
Load up.
Oh!
Oh boy, it's gonna take forever to charge.
Wait, we can do it now, though.
Right?
We can do that now?
Trinity shield and sacred heart!
Heels all red hearts.
Damage multiplier.
Less tears, more damage.
That's gonna bring us to full red hearts now.
I don't know what that's gonna do now, but sure.
And we have this one.
What's that?
Another fool!
I don't think we need that, but okay.
Oh, wait, Mr. Me!
Oh, I could also take that, I guess.
Jira.
This is a crazy-ass shop!
Please, all duplicates... I mean, let's just use that.
Jira.
Not that it matters too much.
Um, give me that one.
So, what is the effect with this?
Let's see.
Wisps will unlock chests and open doors after room clear.
I don't know.
Not really feeling that.
I think I'll stick to this one.
Donate a bunch of money.
Until it breaks.
There we go.
And now we're gonna go down to the treasure room.
This is a very weird run, but I like it.
Okay.
Whoa, they have a lot of HP.
No problem.
Uh, oh, I thought that was an item I could take.
I don't remember what five is.
What is five?
Oh, restart current floor.
That is kind of exciting, actually.
I think I'm gonna do that, but not yet.
Treasure room first, of course.
Spiders.
Flies.
Okay.
Headless.
Oh, that's gonna make us three out of three and conjoined!
Definitely want to take that.
Check this out.
Oh, yeah.
That's sick.
Not bad.
Oh, that's just gonna do the other side, I guess.
Honestly, I don't even think I need my little guys anymore, like the little bomb dudes.
I'm chilling without that, you know?
I just have a lot of damage.
What's that?
Small rock.
What?
Nine damage?
Are you shitting me?
Oh!
Why is that so much damage?
What's up with that?
That is so weird.
I am so confused.
Wheel of fortune.
Why not?
I don't know what to spend my money on, otherwise.
Gonna spend all of it.
Nah, save some of it, because we're gonna have another, uh, shop.
And then we restart the floor, right?
Uh, yeah.
Oh, god.
What was that?
Uh, blue heart, I guess.
See, now we're at 12 damage again.
I don't know what happened.
I don't know why we had so much damage just now.
Something was affecting us, and I don't know why.
Okay, let's go reset.
We're gonna get all new items now.
Yeah, let's hit it inside here.
Oh!
Uh...
Maybe I'll actually keep that.
I'm not even kidding.
Kamikaze is cool, but...
Maybe it's time.
Let me think.
So if I take this...
Oh, man.
This is a big decision I need to make here.
I'm gonna take this first.
Check it out.
We're gonna do this.
We're gonna spawn as many as we can of these.
There we go.
Wait, we lost the red heart.
Oh, because we took the thing, right?
One more.
There we go.
Now we're full on this.
Now I'm gonna switch.
And now I'll leave this behind.
It's a big moment.
I left it behind.
It's done.
Who knows?
Maybe we find something even better.
Copy's head!
Item spawns wisps instead of flies.
Yo, this is pretty good.
That's, uh...
That's pretty good.
I think I'll take that instead.
Thank you.
Oh, yeah.
That's a fantastic one.
Uh, wait.
Yeah, just give me that, I guess.
Nice.
This is carpet bombing here.
I'm gonna have so many wisps I can make at all times.
Because I have a bank.
Ooh, what do we have here?
That's key!
That's interesting.
Unlock's locks on contact can be donated to Keymaster.
Dude, I wonder if this will work on the outline at home.
I feel like I gotta take it.
We gotta try this.
It's too interesting.
Something's gotta happen with that key, right?
Also, I need to see, what is the interaction here?
Uh, can be donated to Keymaster.
Whoa!
You probably get something really crazy if you do that.
Oh, if I get the opportunity, I'm gonna try that.
I am too curious.
Oh, shit!
Wow, it's chaos.
What is even happening here?
I think I'm just gonna start using my key.
It's a waste of energy, otherwise.
Wait, how did I...
Oh, the spiky rocks.
Oh, god!
Why am I taking damage?
I really shouldn't have picked up the thing that gave me bombs whenever I take damage.
It's not good.
Look at this, I got key wisps now.
Oh, I also know why I have so much damage now.
It's because of the crown, of course.
Uh, plug the current room, gain health, speed down...
That's actually not bad.
I'm gonna keep that.
I don't think I'm doing much with that, actually.
Yeah, I'm already full.
Let's go to shop.
And look for secrets.
Wait, oh, here's a secret.
Whoa!
Holy shit!
Uh, oh wait, these are my guys.
Dude, we can duplicate in here.
Let's do it.
Just for fun.
The sun!
It's really good for me.
We have strength, more strength, judgment.
We can spawn a beggar.
And we have the tower.
I kind of don't want that, so I'm gonna go out here and...
Oh, the world, use it.
Oh, right, we can already see it.
Dude, this is so overwhelming.
Just reuse the cards.
Get them out of here.
Why not?
Get it done.
Credit card makes any purchasable items and pick up the current room free.
Okay, we're going to the shop with that.
Right now, before we do anything else.
That sounds awesome.
I got mom's credit card!
Wait, wait, so...
Coupon.
This is so weird.
It's all free.
What is the interaction with this?
Wisps are destroyed when anything is purchased.
Triple shot they have.
That's kind of not bad.
Is there anything combat related with the key?
Not really.
So, it's actually not the best thing to just have.
Empress.
I'm going to donate more money.
Oh, wait, I can't.
We got to go check out the rest of the cards.
I'm kind of at a loss for words right now.
This is too crazy.
I think, honestly, the strategist will have two sons.
Blow them up.
I need money equals power.
A beggar?
You know what?
Let's give them all the money.
I guess we'll spend my money on something.
Give me like an item.
Okay, the bean.
Wait, last X1 auto wisp creates a poison.
That could be good, actually.
Let me see here.
Did that spawn?
Oh, it did.
It did.
Yo!
Ah, last for the room, right?
Okay, yeah.
Another credit card.
But yeah, I mean, I'm taking a son.
I'm taking two sons.
There we go.
I mean, this is just what I need to do.
I'm gonna leave this key here.
Actually, no.
I am so conflicted.
Give me these.
The stars.
Do we have a treasure room yet?
We do.
Dude, I am overwhelmed by everything that's happening right now.
I'm just gonna...
I'm gonna...
Wait, where's my other son?
There it is.
I'm taking this.
We gotta try it, man.
I'm too excited.
Okay.
Honestly, I'm ready.
Let's just move.
My brain can't handle it.
We gotta go.
Just simplify the shit out of my situation.
Okay, here we go.
How can you have spent our savings?
We should just be destroying walls.
Whoa, look at this.
Nice.
Let's see what we get.
What kind of eye?
Proptosis.
Here's getting a large damage bonus, but have much shorter range.
Ooh, wait, how much shorter?
We currently have not that much range, you know.
But it is a large amount, and with the crown, it's gonna be twice that.
So I don't know.
Take it.
We'll see how it feels.
Ooh, that's really bad.
I thought it would be more than that.
Yikes.
Oh, man.
That's bad.
Wait, we got something over here.
I think I did loot everything on these floors.
This one should be clean.
No, never mind.
Ooh, hold on now.
This could be good.
This is permanent.
It's not just for the room.
I like that.
Yeah, especially now that my range is so short, I need to...
I gotta play safe, man.
We're gonna play it like...
We have to win this.
I really don't want to lose.
I'm so confused by the little dude spawning.
Wait, what is that black thing on the...
Oh, it's the ladder, okay.
We're gonna have so many wisps, because we have the inner circle with the bombs, and then we're gonna have an outer circle now.
That's just another element to Bethany.
You know, if you can switch out your active, so that you end up with wisps on different radii.
Pretty sick.
Getting a lot of cards here.
What's that?
Hierophant?
Yeah, sure.
Thank you.
Emperor, no thanks.
I'm surprised I still have all these bomb wisps.
What's that?
Endless, nameless.
Chance to spawn a copy of a card pillow rune that was used.
Ooh.
At this point, it may actually be okay.
I don't know if I want to have a child's heart anymore.
I'm good with that.
The hermit.
Give me that.
Stars.
Okay, moving on.
Wait, we got a healing here.
There we go.
Now we move.
We can still optimize a little.
Just like your father.
Look at who he has to look up to.
Shut up, man.
Shut up.
Just keep pushing me like this.
I'm leaving.
Leave.
We'll be fine without you.
I'm missing page.
Black hearts and dried hustle.
Nah, I'm good.
I think we're gonna kick ass honestly.
I think it's gonna be an easy one.
Like, we have a shit ton of damage.
Especially with two sons.
Oh, yeah,
I ran into my own bomb there.
That was not great.
I did it again.
Fucking bombs!
The problem is when I get hit, it spawns more.
And then it gets worse and worse and worse.
It's a bad circle, you know?
Gotta be something in here.
I remember this room.
I think this was the room that had...
Oh, no, wait, that was from another run.
I'm getting things mixed.
Okay, let's leave.
If we can find the leaf space.
Leave room.
Okay.
The Empress.
Dagas.
Do we have a...
May as well use that.
Dude, Magician...
He's not gonna be too good, actually, because we have such short range anyway.
So it doesn't matter.
It's better with the sun.
Give him all the money.
Okay.
Oh, yeah, we also heal passively.
So if we're really optimizing here, we could just wait.
Not exciting, honestly, but...
I am actually considering getting rid of my bomb wisps, because they will hurt me.
Because if I move forwards while shooting, I will hurt myself.
And I can see that happening a lot during a boss fight.
Here I get to be more calculated, right?
But the Chariots.
Don't think I want that.
I just lost a lot of flies there.
Okay, let's leave.
Caves one.
Man, I shouldn't have taken the goddamn range reduction.
It is so not worth.
Also, I'm actually losing my bomb guys.
Oh, nice.
Okay, good.
Now we just gotta save that.
So I'm losing my bomb guys now.
So that means I need to start thinking in different ways.
I need to get in close and act like a shotgun instead.
I still have two left, but you know.
They're gonna disappear soon.
Oh, fuck.
Whip work.
Guys, this may be it.
My shots actually reach further now.
Look.
That is so huge.
Massive upgrade.
I can't believe it.
The whip worm came in clutch.
Oh my god, stop.
Oh, that's actually healing.
I don't need it.
Now we have the sun and crack key.
Yeah, and when we're at full health, we do a lot of damage.
So we kind of got to stay there.
We need flawless execution.
And we can get it by just spamming wisps, you know.
Yeah, okay, we're done here.
Now to remember where the light was.
Here it is.
Oh, basement.
Oh, I thought that was the last one we were in.
Damn.
Wait, I see it.
Oh, treasure room is back there.
It doesn't matter.
I have this crazy buffer of wisps around me.
So chances of actually staying at max HP is kind of high.
As long as we can keep that up, you know.
Yo, he wants keys?
I got you.
More range!
Yeah!
Massive!
That is exactly what I need.
Wow, this guy just gives me all the things.
Too bad we don't have more keys, huh?
I'm gonna save the last key.
Let's blow him up.
Oh, we can't.
I got another key there.
A beggar?
Another?
Wait.
Oh, cool.
Now we can give him coins.
He handed the torch over to the next guy.
He brought in a substitute.
I mean, okay.
Whatever.
I am so powerful.
I think we can just go, honestly.
Like, I don't even feel like clearing anymore.
Just go.
Oh, man, we don't have spectral tears.
That's the only thing that would make this perfect.
I just can't do this.
Range is good now.
Panic button.
No.
Not that good.
The boogers are gonna go hard, by the way.
They may even be my biggest type of damage.
During a prolonged fight.
What's that?
Oh, it's all my little baby guys.
High priestess?
No, thanks.
We've reached maximum wisps.
Here we go.
Let's really nail it.
Let's do this.
Myo soda is up to four uncollected pick-ups from the previous four.
That's not gonna matter for me.
I don't care about that.
Whatever.
Okay, here we go.
Bethany, you're free.
What's this?
Mom's purse?
Uh, oh!
Wait, I guess I can go back then and grab the other one.
Then I'll take it.
Wait, up here.
Why not?
I don't think it's gonna matter to me right now, though.
Let's nail it.
What, what, uh, Callus?
Where'd you come from?
Confusing.
No idea why that was there.
All right, let's nail Dogma.
Here we go, Bethany.
The damage is good.
It's very good.
This guy is so dead.
Oh, damn.
Perfection?
Wait, what was that?
You saw that?
What the hell was that about?
Okay, he's dead.
Good night.
Next.
Wait, did I just destroy that?
How did I do that?
I don't even know how I just did that.
Oh, probably my Wisp?
That's probably what that was.
Oh, I can destroy these little projectiles, too?
I had no idea.
Oh, you're dead as well.
You are so dead, son.
Shit, we're using the sun already.
I want to stay at max damage.
You may think I'm crazy.
I'm not.
I'm not crazy.
Okay, jar of wisps has appeared.
I'm so sad, guys.
This could have been a five on the win streak if I didn't have that really annoying Bethany start.
But it was still good.
Decent all around.
We had a lot of wins today.
A lot of wins.
We had a small moment of tilt.
But other than that, pretty good.
Next time, we're going to try the new Bethany.
It was an early stream today, actually, yeah.
I don't know.
I just felt like playing.
Like, I didn't want to wait.
It's a little selfish, but, you know, that's what bots are for as well.
Some people can now become a bot gang, and people that normally don't catch the stream got the opportunity to watch this one, you know?
Because it's normally a little too late for those people.
You can restart by holding R.
Oh, yeah, right.
That's true.
I forgot about that.
I actually didn't know about it.
I just kind of didn't think about it.
I should be doing that, I guess.
Maybe, Alexis.
Maybe I'll do two times Isaac or two times Sims.
It depends how I feel.
I would say expect, like, me to alternate between them one on one.
But it could also change.
It depends.
Yeah, exactly.
It's whatever I feel like.
We're making a lot of progress on unlocks, guys.
Yeah, the stream ended.
We started early today, Svario.
If that's why you're confused.
How come the Sims last, like, five hours?
Because the Sims is awesome, dude.
And it's a lot of fun.
I suggest you play it.
And it's very, very addicting.
It's not as intensive as Isaac, so you can naturally go for longer.
How
many secrets have I unlocked?
I don't know.
Quite a lot.
Should play Gunfire Reborn.
I think it's on my backlog already, actually.
Let me see.
Gunfire...
No, actually, it's not.
I'll add it.
It's a good roguelike, huh?
So you said Gunfire Reborn.
Okay, I'm gonna add it.
Yeah, that's the link to the backlog.
Sims 1 is still the best.
I mean, it is just a classic.
It really is.
That game is unbelievably amazing.
And it's also super difficult.
If you think The Sims is an easy game, you're wrong.
The Sims 1 is absolutely gonna destroy you for a while.
I think it depends, Peanut Bumter.
I think some people say 2 is better.
Some people say 1 is better.
It's, you know, it's a preference thing, I think.
I have very good memories of Sims 2, but I don't remember much.
Except that it's really good.
Did Oliver end up using, like, any of the 50 guppies hit charge?
I did.
If you paid attention, I was actually always keeping my wisps at maximum.
There is an upper limit on it, and I tried to keep it going.
After everyone, yeah.
People have been suggesting the Neil.
Fun website as a short stream thing?
What?
The Neil?
Like flash games or what?
Sandboxels, cursor camp, internet road trip, password game, space elevator.
I don't even know.
Is it something we can play together?
Or is it a single player thing?
Looks like one of those sites where you have multiplayer stuff.
And single player, okay.
Huh, okay.
Maybe we'll do, like, a Neil stream then, where we talk about Neil.
It's games and stuff by Neil, is what the website says.
Guys, I'm gonna go immediately.
I have some things I need to take care of.
Tomorrow, I gotta go to a bigger city, to Copenhagen, and also do some stuff.
I gotta prepare for that.
So, no stream tomorrow, but definitely the day after that.
And it's probably gonna be The Sims.
But it could also be Isaac, depends.
Thanks for watching.
I'm gonna be out of your hair.
Bye bye.